fairygodboss.com 2019-07-29

# Privacy Policy | Fairygodboss

## Fairygodboss Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: May 31, 2019**

This “ **Privacy Policy** ” describes the privacy practices of Fairygodboss, Inc. and our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “ **Fairygodboss** ,” “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, or “ **our** ”) in connection with the [http://www.fairygodboss.com](http://www.fairygodboss.com/) website and any other website that we own or control and which posts or links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “ **Services”** ), and the rights and choices available to individuals with respect to their information.

We provide important information for individuals located in the European Union, European Economic Area, and United Kingdom (collectively, “ **Europe** ” or “ **European** ”) below.

### Table of Contents

  * Personal Information We Collect
  * How We Use Your Personal Information
  * How We Share Your Personal Information
  * Your Choices
  * Other Sites and Services
  * Security Practices
  * International Data Transfers
  * Children
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * How to Contact Us
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * Notice to European Users
  * Cookie Policy

### Personal Information We Collect

 **Information you provide to us.   **Personal information about you provide to us through the Service or otherwise includes:

  *  **Business and personal contact information** , such as your first and last name, email and mailing addresses, phone number, professional title and company name.
  *  **Content you choose to upload to the Services** , such as text, images, audio, and video, along with the metadata associated with the files you upload.
  *  **Profile information,  **such as your username and password that you may set to establish an online account with us, your interests and preferences.
  *  **Registration information,  **such as information that may be related to a service, an account or an event you register for.
  *  **Feedback or correspondence** , such as information you provide when you contact us with questions, feedback, or otherwise correspond with us online.
  *  **Mailing information,** such as your city, state, country of residence, and postal code.
  *  **Usage information** , such as information about how you use the Services and interact with us, including information associated with any content you upload to the websites or otherwise submit to us, and information you provide when you use any interactive features of the Services.
  *  **Marketing information** , such as information such your preferences for receiving communications about our activities, events, and publications, and details about how you engage with our communications.
  *  **Professional information** , such as professional credentials and skills, educational and work history, and other information of the type that may be included on a resume or curriculum vitae.
  *  **Other information** that we may collect which is not specifically listed here, but which we will use in accordance with this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed at the time of collection.

 **Information we obtain from social media platforms.  **We may maintain pages for our Company on social media platforms, such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Google, YouTube, Instagram, and other third party platforms. When you visit or interact with our pages on those platforms, the platform provider’s privacy policy will apply to your interactions and their collection, use and processing of your personal information. You or the platforms may provide us with information through the platform, and we will treat such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

If you choose to login to the Services via a third party platform or social media network, or otherwise connect your account on the third party platform or network to your account through the Services, we may collect information from that platform or network. For example, this information may include your Facebook username, user ID, profile picture, cover photo, and networks to which you belong (e.g., school, workplace). You may also have the opportunity to provide us with additional information via the third party platform or network, such as a list of your friends or connections and your email address.  You can read more about your privacy choices in the “Third party platforms or social media networks” portion of the “Your Choices” section.

 **Information we obtain from other third parties.   **We may receive personal information about you from third party sources. For example, a business partner may share your contact information with us if you have expressed interest in learning specifically about our products or services, or the types of products or services we offer. We may obtain your personal information from other third parties, such as marketing partners and publicly available sources.

 **Cookies and Other Information Collected by Automated Means  **

We, our service providers, our business partners and other third parties may automatically log information about you, your computer or mobile device, and activity occurring on or through the Services. The information that may be collected automatically includes your computer or mobile device operating system type and version number, manufacturer and model, device identifier (such as the Google Advertising ID or Apple ID for Advertising), browser type, screen resolution, IP address, the website you visited before browsing to our website, general location information such as city, state or geographic area; and information about your use of and actions on the Services, such as pages or screens you viewed, how long you spent on a page or screen, navigation paths between pages or screens, information about your activity on a page or screen, access times, and length of access.  Our service providers and business partners may collect this type of information over time and across third party websites and mobile applications. 

On our webpages, this information is collected using cookies, browser web storage (also known as locally stored objects, or “LSOs”), Flash-based LSOs (also known as “Flash cookies”), web beacons, and similar technologies, and our emails may also contain web beacons. 

SeeCookie Policyfor more information.

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We use your personal information for the following purposes and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection:

 **To operate the Service.   **We use your personal information to:

  * provide, operate and improve the Service
  * provide information about our products and services
  * establish and maintain your user profile on the Service
  * communicate with you about the Service, including by sending you announcements, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages
  * communicate with you about events or contests in which you participate
  * understand your needs and interests, and personalize your experience with the Service and our communications
  * provide support and maintenance for the Service
  * to respond to your requests, questions and feedback

 **For research and development.   **We analyze use of the Service to analyze and improve the Service and to develop new products and services, including by studying user demographics and use of the Services.

 **To send you marketing and promotional communications.   **We may send you Fairygodboss-related marketing communications as permitted by law. You will have the ability to opt-out of our marketing and promotional communications as described in the Opt out of marketing section below. ** **

 **To display advertisements.  **We work with advertising partners to display advertisements on the Services. These advertisements are delivered by our advertising partners and may be targeted based on your use of the Services or your activity elsewhere online. To learn more about your choices in connection with advertisements, please see the section below titled “Targeted online advertising.”

 **To process employment applications.  **We use personal information, such as information submitted to us in a job application, to process employment applications, such as by evaluating a job candidate for an employment activity, and monitoring recruitment statistics.

 **To comply with law.  **We use your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities.

 **With your consent.   **In some cases we may specifically ask for your consent to collect, use or share your personal information, such as when required by law.  

 **To create anonymous data.   **We may create anonymous data from your personal information and other individuals whose personal information we collect.  We make personal information into anonymous data by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable to you.  We may use this anonymous data and share it with third parties for our lawful business purposes, including to analyze and improve the Service and promote our business.  

We do not share your personal information with third parties without your consent, except in the following circumstances or as described in this Privacy Policy:

 **Affiliates.   **We may share your personal information with our corporate parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates, for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

 **Service providers.**  We may share your personal information with third party companies and individuals that provide services on our behalf or help us operate the Services (such as customer support, hosting, analytics, email delivery, marketing, and database management services). These third parties may use your personal information only as directed or authorized by us and in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, and are prohibited from using or disclosing your information for any other purpose.

 **Virtual Career Fair employers**. We may disclose any information provided by job applicants during a Virtual Career Fair (i.e., professional information, as discussed above) to recruiters from participating companies. 

 **Third party platforms and social media networks.  **If you have enabled features or functionality that connect the Service to a third party platform or social media network (such as by logging in to the Services using your account with the third party, providing your API key or similar access token for the Service to a third party, or otherwise linking your account with the Service to a third party’s services), we may disclose the personal information that you authorized us to share. We do not control the third party’s use of your personal information.

 **Other Users of the Service and the Public.  **We may provide functionality that enables you to disclose personal information to other users of the Service or the public. For instance, you may be able to maintain a user profile with information about yourself that you can make available to other users or the public. You may also be able to submit content to the Services (such as comments, reviews, surveys, blogs, photos, and videos), and we will display your name, username, and a link to your user profile along with the content you submit. We do not control how other users or third parties use any personal information that you make available to other users or the public.

 **Business transfers.**   We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our business or assets, including your personal information, in connection with a business transaction (or potential business transaction) such as a corporate divestiture, merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy or dissolution. In such a case, we will make reasonable efforts to require the recipient to honor this Privacy Policy.

### Your Choices

In this section, we describe the rights and choices available to all users. Users who are located within the European Union can find additional information about their rights below.

 **Access or Update Your Information.  **If you have registered for an account with us, you may review and update certain personal information in your account profile by logging into the account.

 **Opt out of marketing communications.** You may opt out of marketing-related emails by following the opt-out or unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email, or by contacting us at [info@fairygodboss.com](mailto:info@fairygodboss.com). You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails.

 **Cookies & Browser Web Storage.  **We may allow service providers and other third parties to use cookies and similar technologies to track your browsing activity over time and across the Service and third party websites. For more details, see our Cookie Policy.

 **Targeted online advertising.  **Some of the business partners that collect information about users’ activities on or through the Service may be members of organizations or programs that provide choices to individuals regarding the use of their browsing behavior or mobile application usage for purposes of targeted advertising. 

Users may opt out of receiving targeted advertising on websites through members of the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or the Digital Advertising Alliance by clicking [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). European users may opt out of receiving targeted advertising on websites through members of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance by clicking [here](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), selecting the user’s country, and then clicking “Choices” (or similarly titled link). Please note that we also may work with companies that offer their own opt-out mechanisms and may not participate in the opt-out mechanisms that we linked above.

In addition, your mobile device settings may provide functionality to limit our, or our partners’, ability to engage in ad tracking or targeted advertising using the Google Advertising ID or Apple ID for Advertising associated with your mobile device.

If you choose to opt-out of targeted advertisements, you will still see advertisements online but they may not be relevant to you. Even if you do choose to opt out, not all companies that serve online behavioral advertising are included in this list, so you may still receive some cookies and tailored advertisements from companies that are not listed.

 **Do Not Track.** Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals.  To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

 **Choosing not to share your personal information.  **Where we are required by law to collect your personal information, or where we need your personal information in order to provide the Service to you, if you do not provide this information when requested (or you later ask to delete it), we may not be able to provide you with our services.  We will tell you what information you must provide to receive the Service by designating it as required at the time of collection or through other appropriate means.

 **Connecting via Facebook and/or Gmail.  **If you choose to connect to the Service via Facebook or Gmail or any other social media service, you may have the ability to limit the information that we may obtain from the third party at the time you login to the Service using the third party’s authentication service or otherwise connect your account. Subsequently, you may be able to control your settings through the third party’s platform or service. For example, you may access and change your settings through the Facebook [settings page](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=applications). If you withdraw our ability to access certain information from a third party platform or social media network, that choice will not apply to information that we have already received from that third party.

### Other Sites and Services

The Service may contain links to other websites and other online services operated by third parties. These links are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third party. In addition, our content may be included on web pages or online services that are not associated with us. We do not control third party websites or online services, and we are not responsible for their actions. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the collection, use and sharing of your personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of the other websites and online services you use.

### Security Practices.

The security of your personal information is important to us.  We employ a number of organizational, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information we collect.  However, security risk is inherent in all internet and information technologies and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. 

### International Data Transfers. 

We are headquartered in the United States and have service providers in other countries, and your personal information may be transferred to the United States or other locations outside of your state, province, or country where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your state, province, or country.

European Union users should read the important information provided below about transfer of personal information outside of the European Union. 

### Children.

As a general rule, children are not allowed to use the Services, and we do not collect personal information from them. We define "children" as follows:

  * Residents outside of Europe: anyone under 13 years old; and
  * Residents of Europe: anyone under 16 years old, or the age needed to consent to the processing of personal data in your country of residence.

If we learn that we have collected personal information of a child without the consent of the child’s parent or guardian, we will delete it. We encourage parents with concerns to contact us.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the date of this Privacy Policy and posting it on the Service. We may also provide notification of changes in another way that we believe is reasonably likely to reach you, such as via e-mail (if you have an account where we have your contact information) or another manner through the Services.

Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our posting the new terms and/or upon implementation of the new changes on the Services (or as otherwise indicated at the time of posting). In all cases, your continued use of the Services after the posting of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the terms of the modified Privacy Policy.

### How to Contact Us

Please direct any questions or comments about this Policy or privacy practices to [info@fairygodboss.com](mailto:info@fairygodboss.com). You may also write to us via postal mail at:

    Fairygodboss, Inc.

    Attn: Legal – Privacy

 **    **15 West 38th Street, 5th Floor

    New York, NY 10018 

### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code section 1798.83, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to us via email at [info@fairygodboss.com](mailto:info@fairygodboss.com). You must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in your request and include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

### Notice to European Users

The information provided in this “Notice to European Users” section applies only to individuals in Europe.

 **Personal information.  **References to “personal information” in this Privacy Policy are equivalent to “personal data” governed by European data protection legislation. 

 **Controller.  **Fairygodboss, Inc. is the controller of your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy for purposes of European data protection legislation.  

 **Legal bases for processing.   **We use your personal information only as permitted by law. Our legal bases for processing the personal information described in this Privacy Policy are described in the list below.

  * Processing purpose ** ** (click link for details) _Details regarding each processing purpose listed below are provided in the section above titled “How We Use Your Personal Information.”_
    *  **Legal basis**

  *  **To operate the Service  
**
    * Processing is necessary to perform the contract governing our provision of the Services or to take steps that you request prior to signing up for the Services.  If we have not entered into a contract with you, we process your personal information based on our legitimate interest in providing the Service you access and request.  

  *  **To administer events, For research and development, To send you marketing communications, To display advertisements, To process employment applications, To create anonymous data**
    * These activities constitute our legitimate interests.  We do not use your personal information for these activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).

  *  **To comply with law**
    * Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations.

  *  **With your consent**
    * Processing is based on your consent.  Where we rely on your consent you have the right to withdraw it any time in the manner indicated when you consent or in the Service.

 **Use for new purposes.  **We may use your personal information for reasons not described in this Privacy Policy where permitted by law and the reason is compatible with the purpose for which we collected it.  If we need to use your personal information for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and explain the applicable legal basis. 

 **Sensitive personal information.**  We ask that you not provide us with any sensitive personal information (e.g., social security numbers, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Services, or otherwise to us. 

If you provide us with any sensitive personal information to us when you use the Services, you must consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal information, you must not submit such sensitive personal information through our Services.

 **Retention**

We retain personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which we collected it, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, to establish or defend legal claims, or for fraud prevention purposes.  

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information, the purposes for which we process your personal information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. 

When we no longer require the personal information we have collected about you, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.  If we anonymize your personal information (so that it can no longer be associated with you), we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

 **Your rights**

European data protection laws give you certain rights regarding your personal information.  If you are located within the European Union, you may ask us to take the following actions in relation to your personal information that we hold:

  *  **Access.**  Provide you with information about our processing of your personal information and give you access to your personal information.
  *  **Correct.**  Update or correct inaccuracies in your personal information.
  *  **Delete.**  Delete your personal information.
  *  **Transfer.**  Transfer a machine-readable copy of your personal information to you or a third party of your choice.
  *  **Restrict.**  Restrict the processing of your personal information.
  *  **Object.**  Object to our reliance on our legitimate interests as the basis of our processing of your personal information that impacts your rights.  

You may submit these requests by email or to our postal address provided above. We may request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and process your request. Applicable law may require or permit us to decline your request. If we decline your request, we will tell you why, subject to legal restrictions. If you would like to submit a complaint about our use of your personal information or our response to your requests regarding your personal information, you may contact us or submit a complaint to the data protection regulator in your jurisdiction. You can find your data protection regulator [here](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en).

### Cross-Border Data Transfer

If we transfer your personal information out of Europe to a country not deemed by the European Commission to provide an adequate level of personal information protection, the transfer will be performed:

  * Pursuant to the recipient’s compliance with standard contractual clauses, EU-US Privacy Shield (or Swiss-US Privacy Shield, as applicable) or Binding Corporate Rules
  * Pursuant to the consent of the individual to whom the personal information pertains
  * As otherwise permitted by applicable European requirements.

You may contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal information out of Europe.
